DEVIN LIM

Seattle, WA · devin@devinl.im · (253) 343-7980 · github.com/davay · linkedin.com/in/devinlim

Product-focused Project Manager/Software Engineer with 3 years of experience leading development and design of large-scale Fraud Protection systems. Demonstrated ability to adapt to a wide range of technologies and situations. Seeking opportunities to create fun, great products and to further diversify my skill set through Data Science.

EDUCATION

Seattle UniversitySeattle, WAMS in Data ScienceSeptember 2023 - PresentSeattle UniversitySeattle, WABS in Computer Science, cum laudeSeptember 2018 - June 2020

Experience

Microsoft Redmond, WA

Software Engineer, via Centific and MAQ Software

October 2020 - October 2023

Fraud Protection Tools Team

- Led a team of over 10 onshore and offshore developers building Microsoft's Fraud Protection ecosystem on .NET and Azure
- Client-side: Served as both an Individual Contributor and a Technical Project Manager, key contributor in the design of new feature requirements and adherence to compliance standards, including GDPR
- Vendor-side: Served as a Delivery Manager, responsible for hiring, coaching, and risk management

Amazon Seattle, WA

Student Intern, via Seattle University

October 2019 - June 2020

Amazon Care Team

- Built a WebRTC video call web-app with Node.js and Express
- · Built a robust, automated AWS pipeline that collects and analyzes information from individual calls
- Built a regression model to quantify call quality based on WebRTC metrics, visualized on the Elastic Stack

Polyverse CorporationBellevue, WACompiler Engineer InternJuly 2019 - September 2019

Co-Inventor of U.S. Patent 10,733,303: Polymorphic Code Translation Systems And Methods

 Researched methods to provide 100% mitigation of deserialization attacks through JVM token scrambling, which aims to prevent RCE attacks such as Equifax breach

MG2 CorporationSeattle, WAIT Support Specialist InternJuly 2018 - September 2018

Maintained, prevented, and resolved issues within the overall IT system

Skills

Languages: Python, HTML/CSS, Javascript/Typescript, R, C#, Bash, SQL, KQL

Data Science: Understanding of machine learning methods such as classification, clustering, and regression

Familiar with statistical and causal inference techniques in the context of experimental design

Data Technologies: Pandas, NumPy, Fastai, Scikit-learn, Seaborn, Tidyverse

Software Technologies: .NET + Razor, ARM Templates, Node.js, Elastic Stack, WebRTC, OpenTelemetry

UNIX: Daily use & tinkering of Linux systems for 6+ years

Experienced in using various UNIX tools and shell scripting for automated, efficient workflow

Cloud Platforms: Experienced with large-scale robust systems in Azure (incl. Azure DevOps), AWS, and GCP

IT: Windows Enterprise, Active Directory, Cisco switches, ManageEngine, Barracuda Networks